(Raj:)I appreciate the apology,
(Raj:)but it's really not necessary.
(Raj:)I overstepped my bounds.
(Howard:)No, Raj, you've been great.
(Howard:)I just, I need to start
doing my part around here.
BERNADETTE:
I hear that.
(Raj:)Well, if that's the case,
(Raj:)is there anything
I can do to help?
(Howard:)Well, not right now.
(Howard:)But we could try out
that microphone you got us,
(Howard:)and listen to
the baby's heartbeat.
(Howard:)Really?
It's okay if I listen with you?!
(Bernadette:)Of course.
(Raj:)Can I squirt the ultrasound
jelly on your stomach?
(Howard:)Hey, look at that.
(Howard:)It's weird again.
(door opens)
(Leonard:)Okay, you have
(Leonard:)every right to be mad.
(Leonard:)And what you said is true.
(Leonard:)You do make more money than me.
(Leonard:)So I had no right
to do what I did.
(Leonard:)And I'm so sorry.
(Leonard:)I hope you can forgive me.
(Penny:)How long have you had
this secret account?
(Leonard:)A couple years,
but I just put a few bucks aside
(Leonard:)every month for emergencies.
(Penny:)Well, how much you got in there?
$6,427.
$47 once my nana's
birthday check gets here.